<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Reality Check-Mate</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="my_map_api_key" translatable="false">AIzaSyBoQfRh77h_NBBzVxfyW9pRsaP178Vp7u8</string>
    <string name="heading_activity">Daily Goal: </string>
    <string name="generate">Generate</string>
    <string name="Display">Display</string>
    <string name="tap_to_display">Tap To Display Random Activity:</string>
    <string name="helptext">Use these activites as a way of actively engaging in your recovery. If the difficulty is too high, try changing to a lower difficulty activity.</string>
    <string name="Difficulty">Difficulty:</string>
    <string name="number" translatable="false">0/10</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_one">Practice active listening: Instead of always talking about yourself and your accomplishments, make an effort to listen to others and engage in meaningful conversations.</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_two">Give compliments to others: Make it a habit to give genuine compliments to others on their strengths and achievements, rather than constantly seeking validation for your own.</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_three">Help someone in need: Volunteering your time and skills to help someone who is less fortunate can help you gain perspective and lower your ego.</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_four">Admit your mistakes: Instead of always trying to appear perfect, admit your mistakes and take responsibility for them. This can show humility and help you grow.</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_five">Do something anonymously: Perform a good deed without seeking recognition or praise, such as donating to a charity anonymously or helping a stranger in need.</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_six">Accept constructive criticism: Instead of becoming defensive when someone offers constructive criticism, listen to their feedback and use it to improve yourself.</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_seven">Take a break from social media: Constantly seeking validation and attention on social media can feed your ego. Take a break from social media to focus on real-life relationships and activities.</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_eight">Share credit: When working on a team or collaborating with others, make sure to share credit for successes and accomplishments.</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_nine">Practice gratitude: Focusing on what you are grateful for can help you appreciate what you have and minimize the need for constant validation and attention.</string>
    <string name="dailygoal_ten">Engage in activities that challenge you: Push yourself out of your comfort zone and engage in activities that challenge you, such as learning a new skill or taking on a difficult project. This can help you stay humble and focused on personal growth.</string>
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_create_notification">Create Notification</string>
    <string name="nav_view_notifications">View Notifications</string>
    <string name="nav_ego_test">Ego Test</string>
    <string name="nav_find_therapy">Find Therapy</string>
    <string name="nav_ego_journal">Ego Journal</string>
    <string name="nav_ego_crush">Ego Crush</string>
    <string name="cusNotif">Please Enter Your Custom Notification:</string>
    <string name="Submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="clear_notifications">Clear Custom Notifications</string>
    <string name="samnot1">You\'re not as perfect as you think. Take a step back and reassess.</string>
    <string name="samnot2">You\'re not the only one with good ideas. Listen to others and collaborate.</string>
    <string name="samnot3">You\'re not the only one who can do this. Trust and delegate tasks.</string>
    <string name="samnot4">Think about other people for once. Show empathy and kindness.</string>
    <string name="samnot5">It\'s okay to be wrong sometimes. Learn from your mistakes.</string>
    <string name="samnot6">You don\'t have to win every argument. Sometimes it\'s better to just let it go.</string>
    <string name="samnot7">Acknowledge and learn from your mistakes. Growth comes from failure.</string>
    <string name="samnot8">Don\'t let success get to your head. Stay humble and grounded.</string>
    <string name="samnot9">Be open to feedback from others. It can help you improve.</string>
    <string name="samnot10">Don\'t put others down to make yourself look better. Lift each other up.</string>
    <string name="samnot11">Practice empathy and understanding towards others. Everyone has their own story.</string>
    <string name="samnot12">Be willing to compromise and collaborate with others. It can lead to better outcomes.</string>
    <string name="samnot13">Take responsibility for your actions and their consequences. Own up to your mistakes.</string>
    <string name="samnot14">Don\'t judge others based on their appearance or background. Get to know them for who they are.</string>
    <string name="samnot15">Challenge yourself to learn and grow every day. It can lead to new opportunities.</string>
    <string name="samnot16">Avoid seeking attention and validation for every little thing. Focus on your own growth.</string>
    <string name="samnot17">Give credit where credit is due. Recognize the efforts of those around you.</string>
    <string name="samnot18">Appreciate the value and contributions of others. We are all part of a team.</string>
    <string name="samnot19">Remember that everyone has their own struggles and challenges. Be kind and supportive.</string>
    <string name="samnot20">Don\'t be afraid to ask for help or support when you need it. We all need a helping hand sometimes.</string>
    <string name="samnot21">Be humble and grateful for what you have. Appreciate the present moment.</string>
    <string name="samnot22">Treat others with kindness and respect, regardless of their status. We are all equal.</string>
    <string name="samnot23">Focus on the journey, not just the destination. Enjoy the process.</string>
    <string name="samnot24">Be mindful of your impact on others and the world around you. Small actions can make a big difference.</string>
    <string name="samnot25">Don\'t take yourself too seriously. Laugh at yourself and enjoy life.</string>
    <string name="SampleNotif">Don\'t let fear hold you back. Take calculated risks and trust in yourself.</string>
    <string name="notifsavetoast">Notification saved</string>
    <string name="clearcustoast">Cleared Custom Notifications</string>
    <string name="Total_Questions">Total Questions</string>
    <string name="This_will_be_the_question">This will be the question</string>
    <string name="Ans_A">Ans A</string>
    <string name="Ans_B">Ans B</string>
    <string name="Ans_C">Ans C</string>
    <string name="Ans_D">Ans D</string>
    <string name="Ego_Log">Ego-Log</string>
    <string name="NEWENTRY">NEW ENTRY</string>
    <string name="not_del">Note deleted</string>
    <string name="del_not">Delete</string>
    <string name="save_note">Note saved</string>
    <string name="Add_New_Entry">Add New Entry</string>
    <string name="Title">Title</string>
    <string name="What_Happened">What Happened?</string>
    <string name="Save_Entry">Save Entry</string>
    <string name="Restart">Restart</string>
    <string name="defeat">Can You Accept Defeat?</string>
    <string name="win">This was supposed to be unbeatable, you\'re allowed an ego boost!</string>
    <string name="lose">You Can Draw, But You Can\'t Win… Life Story?</string>


</resources>